export const gotQuizes = [
  {
    title: "Quiz1",
    data: [
      {
        question: "Question1",
        answers: ["111", "222", "333", "444"],
        correct: "444"
      },
      {
        question: "Question2",
        answers: ["ppp", "ooo", "iii", "uuu"],
        correct: "ooo"
      },
      {
        question: "Question3",
        answers: ["aaa", "sss", "ddd", "fff"],
        correct: "fff"
      },
      {
        question: "Question4",
        answers: ["qq", "ww", "ee", "rr"],
        correct: "ee"
      },
      {
        question: "Question5",
        answers: ["zzz", "xxx", "ccc", "vvv"],
        correct: "xxx"
      }
    ],
    id: 1
  },
  {
    title: "Quiz2",
    data: [
      {
        question: "Question1",
        answers: ["111", "322", "333", "444"],
        correct: "444"
      },
      {
        question: "Question2",
        answers: ["ppp", "zoo", "iii", "uuu"],
        correct: "ooo"
      },
      {
        question: "Question3",
        answers: ["aaa", "sss", "ddd", "fff"],
        correct: "fff"
      },
      {
        question: "Question4",
        answers: ["qq", "ww", "ee", "rr"],
        correct: "ee"
      },
      {
        question: "Question5",
        answers: ["zzz", "xxx", "ccc", "vvv"],
        correct: "xxx"
      }
    ],
    id: 2
  },
  {
    title: "Quiz3",
    data: [
      {
        question: "Question1",
        answers: ["111", "882", "333", "444"],
        correct: "444"
      },
      {
        question: "Question2",
        answers: ["ppp", "ooo", "iii", "uuu"],
        correct: "ooo"
      },
      {
        question: "Question3",
        answers: ["aaa", "sss", "ddd", "fff"],
        correct: "fff"
      },
      {
        question: "Question4",
        answers: ["qq", "ww", "ee", "rr"],
        correct: "ee"
      },
      {
        question: "Question5",
        answers: ["zzz", "xxx", "ccc", "vvv"],
        correct: "xxx"
      }
    ],
    id: 3
  }
];
